[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of Pussy Galores flying school in the motion picture Goldfinger?", "correct_answer": "Flying Circus", "incorrect_answers": ["Winged Spirits", "Golden Angels", "Airborne Amazons"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the unit of power that shows how fast a circuit uses electrical energy?", "correct_answer": "Watt", "incorrect_answers": ["Frequency", "Voltage", "Amp"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which four countries can be seen from Eilat?", "correct_answer": "Israel, Egypt, Jordan, Saudi Arabia", "incorrect_answers": ["Israel, Egypt, Saudi Arabia, Yemen", "Israel, Jordan, Syria, Lebanon", "Israel, Egypt, Jordan, Syria"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the leader of the evil Decepticons in Transformers 2?", "correct_answer": "The Fallen", "incorrect_answers": ["The Dark King", "The Prime", "The Master"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Plastics was the one word career advice given to a befuddled Benjamin Braddock played by Dustin Hoffman in this movie.", "correct_answer": "The Graduate", "incorrect_answers": ["Midnight Cowboy", "Rain Man", "Tootsie"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of people did Jack the Ripper, who inspired many film characters, kill in 1888?", "correct_answer": "Prostitutes", "incorrect_answers": ["Adulterers", "Drunkards", "All of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This is the only RB/soul singer asked by Johnny Carson to perform twice in the same week in The Tonight Show.", "correct_answer": "Patti LaBelle", "incorrect_answers": ["Gladys Knight", "Aretha Franklin", "Whitney Houston"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In what movie did Leonardo DiCaprio star alongside Sharon Stone and Russell Crowe?", "correct_answer": "The Quick and the Dead", "incorrect_answers": ["The Basketball Diaries", "Marvins Room", "The Man in the Iron Mask"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actor plays the villain in the movie Dr. No?", "correct_answer": "Joseph Wiseman", "incorrect_answers": ["Raymond Burr", "Herbert Lom", "Vincent Price"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What South Carolina Senator lived to be one hundred years old while still holding office?", "correct_answer": "Strom Thurmond", "incorrect_answers": ["Mike Mansfield", "James, (Jimmy)  Byrnes", "Fritz Hollings"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What type of meat is used in the preparation of the Indian dish called Bombay duck?", "correct_answer": "Fish", "incorrect_answers": ["Chicken", "Pork", "Beef"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Saw III the shotgun collar was one of Jeffs tests.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}]